Lau Ki Ki, Katie

Mobile: 60973189 katielau.ki@hotmail.com Flat 3215, Shui Chuen House, Tin Shui Est. Tin Shui Wai

Certified Public Accountant with 4+ years of experience of ledger process, prepare management reporting, financial statement, assists in annual, interim& statutory reporting. Bachelor of degree in Accounting. Seeking to leverage accounting expertise and experience into a managerial role.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

Hong Kong TV Shopping Network Company Limited

Sep 2015 to Apr 2017

Assistant Officer

- Preparation of financial statements, management reports
- Perform fixed assets accounting, bank reconciliation, investment, treasury, general ledger
- Perform day to day finance and accounts operations
- Perform ecommerce accounting (revenue & inventory)
- Assisting on annual & interim result announcement, statutory reporting and liaise with external auditor
- Assisting on preparing tax schedule and profit tax return
- Handling ecommerce customer services refund

Tricor Services Limited

Aug 2013 to Sep 2015

Officer

- Handle bookkeeping ,maintain full set of books and accounts of various companies
- Prepare management accounts, breakdowns and other reconciliation schedules, cash flow statements
- Provide payroll processing, treasury

Baker Tilly Hong Kong

Nov 2012 to Jun 2013

Tax Assistant

- Provide basic advisory letters
- Participate in business tax compliance and tax advisory engagements
- Assist in preparing reports and schedules that will be delivered to clients and other parties

EDUCATION

THE OPEN UNIVERSITY OF HONG KONG

Aug 2012

Bachelor of degree with honor - Major accounting (first class honor)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Accounting software: Oracle, Sun account Microsoft Office Applications

CERTIFICATIONS

Hong Kong Institute of Certificated Public Accountant

Jun 2015

(Qualified public accountant)